data =
    '[{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 1", "answer" : "1"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 2", "answer" : "2"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 3", "answer" : "3"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 4", "answer" : "4"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 5", "answer" : "5"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 6", "answer" : "6"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 7", "answer" : "7"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Easy", "question" : "click 8", "answer" : "8"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 9", "answer" : "9"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 10", "answer" : "10"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 11", "answer" : "11"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 12", "answer" : "12"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 13", "answer" : "13"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 14", "answer" : "14"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 15", "answer" : "15"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Normal", "question" : "click 16", "answer" : "16"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 17", "answer" : "17"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 18", "answer" : "18"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 19", "answer" : "19"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 20", "answer" : "20"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 21", "answer" : "21"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 22", "answer" : "22"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 23", "answer" : "23"},' +
    '{"Difficulty" : "Hard", "question" : "click 24", "answer" : "24"}]';